### Contact

satishiyer31@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/satishi (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

SaaS

Software Project Management Enterprise Software

### Languages

Hindi

Tamil

**English** 

### Certifications

Oracle Business Intelligence - Server Architect

RightNow Certification

### Honors-Awards

Oracle - North America Consulting Award

# Satish Iyer

Senior Solutions Consultant at Zendesk

Denver Metropolitan Area

## Summary

Experienced Senior Sales Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Strong sales professional skilled in Requirements Analysis, Enterprise Software, Agile Methodologies, Customer Relationship Management (CRM), and Professional Services.

# Experience

Zendesk

Senior Solutions Consultant June 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Boulder, Colorado, United States

#### Oracle

8 years 4 months

Senior Sales Consultant May 2016 - June 2020 (4 years 2 months)

Boulder, CO

As a service cloud specialist I am responsible for formulating and leading presales technical / functional support activity to prospective clients and customers. I also build and deliver custom product demonstrations which focus on key business drivers, functional requirements and demonstrate the value of our solution for potential customers.

Principal Consultant
March 2012 - April 2016 (4 years 2 months)
Bozeman, MT

Responsible for Implementation & maintenance of enterprise level Oracle Service Cloud Sites. Job duties also include the following

- -Simultaneously manage multiple projects/clients from inception through completion utilizing the Oracle Project Methodology to achieve desired business goals.
- -Apply technical & functional knowledge of the Oracle Service Solution Suite Service, Marketing, Sales, Feedback, Analytics and Chat.

- Analyze customer requirements and understand customer processes & ecosystem to gather and thoroughly document business requirements and determine feasibility of design.
- -Influence business decisions based on leveraging best practices and problem solving skills.
- -Coordinate and prioritize all aspects of projects, including planning, project management & communication, execution and completion.
- Use the Oracle Reporting platform to generate complex reports and metrics.
- -Ensure all projects are delivered successfully on schedule and on budget
- -Engage with customers in regularly scheduled project meetings to update the business owners on the status of the project.
- Identify opportunities to position other service offerings to support clients' long-term, strategic objectives.

RightNow Technologies
Senior Consultant
June 2010 - February 2012 (1 year 9 months)

Tata Consultancy Services
Siebel Analytics/ Oracle Business Intelligence Consultant
January 2006 - May 2010 (4 years 5 months)
BI Consultant

# Education

University of Mumbai Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Electronics